DMITRIY SURNAME

UNITY DEVELOPER

+420 123 456 789 name@gmail.com Prague, Czech Republic



linkedin.com/in/name github.com/name t.me/name

PROFILE

I develop mobile games, create my own projects, try all the current games of the AAA industry. I have experience in launching applications in Google Play, setting up ads and game analytics. I have explored the peculiarities of the Match3 genre well.

SKILLS

UNITY

- Animations, UI, Physics, Editor
 - Shaders (basic knowledge) •
 - Addressables, Asset Bundles
 - PlayMaker, Tweens, UniRx
 - Facebook SDK, AdMob
 - Firebase •

C#

- OOP, SOLID, Patterns
 - LINQ •

TOOLS

- Rider, Visual Studio
 - GIT. TFVC •
 - Jira, Asana, Trello •
- Excel, Google Sheets
 - Photoshop •

COURSES

09.2022-Present PLI | English Course

09.2020-06.2021 GoStudy | Czech Course

09.2019-01.2020 LSE UA | English Course

EXPERIENCE

04.2021-12.2022

Company3 | Unity Developer

Created mechanics in the Match3 part of the game. Implementation meta-game elements (ad units, interactive scenes, shops).

Worked on the custom elements in the editor.

09.2020-03.2021

Company2 | Unity Developer

Support and updating of released projects. Setting up advertising and analytics.

09.2018-08.2020

Company1 | Software Developer

Developed games for touch screen custom computers on Unity, which were built on the UWP. Implementation methods of interaction between Unity and custom SDK.

EDUCATION

2021-2022 (isn't finished)

Master | Web Technology

University of Economics and Business Prague

2016-2020

Bachelor | Factory Automation

Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute Kyiv

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate

Ukrainian Native Russian Native

Czech Upper-Intermediate